(gentle music)
Whether you're setting up a sponsored products campaign or wanting to optimize your existing ads,
Amazon Ads creates recommendations that can help improve your campaign performance.
These recommendations focus on targeting, bidding, and budget strategies, which help set up your
campaigns for success.
Targeting recommendations help show your ads to shoppers based on the keywords or products they
are searching for on Amazon.
Bidding recommendations include a bid amount that can help increase impressions and engagement for
your campaigns.
After reviewing your targeting and bidding settings, it's important to consider budget recommendations,
which help your ads stay active and in budget.
Now, you're ready to start optimizing your campaigns.
Here's how to get started.
Within the Campaign Manager, visit the targeting and budget pages to review past results for all
campaigns.
If you find a specific campaign that you want to adjust, you can go to the Ad Group level to apply
the recommendation.
You may also occasionally receive recommendations via email.
After making any adjustments, it's important to monitor your return on ad spend,
ROAS, to track campaign performance.
If you have questions as you're making optimizations and reviewing your results,
visit the Support Center for more information.